const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "What kind of cars can i get from Vehica Uganda?",
    answer:
      "Buying a vehicle is easy with Vehica Uganda. You can buy online via our website. If you’re new to buying a vehicle online, rest assured that we will assist you with the purchase, and delivery processes.  Learn more by visiting our How to Buy page.",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "How can I buy a car from Vehica Uganda?",
    answer:
      "There are lots of affordable cars on our website including Toyota, Nissan, and Honda. Please check our list of affordable vehicles to see what we currently have in stock.",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "How do I pay for my car?",
    answer:
      "Generally, we accept payments through bank wire transfer. We also accept payments through our Local Offices, PayPal, Mobile Money and Western Union. Learn more by visiting our How to Pay page.",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What are the cheap selling cars?",
    answer:
      "Toyota currently makes the best-selling Japanese car because of their reputation for durability and affordable prices. Please check our list of Toyota vehicles to see what we currently have in stock.",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "How long does the process take?",
    answer:
      "From the time you fill out an application, we’ll get the process started within just a few short hours. In the best circumstances, we can even have you driving away in your new vehicle within just 3 – 4 working days! It’s really that easy.",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Do you sell Auto Parts?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we sell auto parts. Please check our auto parts website to see what we currently have in stock.",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "Which car type can I get at 5 million Ugx?",
    answer:
      "There are a lot of affordable cars on our website including Toyota, Nissan, and Honda. Please check our list of affordable vehicles to see what we currently have in stock.",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "Can I purchase a vehicle if I live out of Uganda?",
    answer:
      "Yes! In fact, we have many buyers from out-of-Uganda. We can either arrange to have the vehicle shipped and delivered to you or you can come drive it home yourself! However; this comes with an extra charge in case of shipping.",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "Do you provide carproof?",
    answer:
      "Yes! All of our vehicles come with a Carproof and a full mechanical fitness inspection.",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question:
      "What types of adaptive equipment can I obtain reimbursement for?",
    answer:
      "Yes, we accept all trades at fair market price. The price will be determined once we appraise your vehicle and determine what your current vehicle is worth.",
  },
]

export default questions
